-嘿  -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
-你在做什么  -我想把沙发搬开
- What are you doing? - I was thinking of moving the couch.
怎么突发奇想要搬沙发了
Why would you want to do that?
我想要个好位置坐
So there'd be a decent place for me to sit?
-瑞秋你本来就有好位置坐  -你的大腿不算
- Rach, there is a decent place. - And your lap does not count.
-来吧  帮我把它搬开  -不
- Come on, help me move this. - No, no, no.
-不  -不
- No? - No.
罗西塔哪也不去
Rosita does not move.
抱歉  罗西塔  是哪位
I'm sorry. Rosita? As in...?
就是哪也不去的那位
As in "Rosita does not move."
就是张椅子  有什么大不了的
It's just a chair. What's the big deal?
它到浴室跟到厨房的距离是一样的
It's the exact equal distance from the bathroom to the kitchen...
而且它所在的角度
...and it's at an angle
使得史迪威不会反光
where you don't get any glare coming off Stevie.
电视史迪威
Stevie the TV?
-有问题  -没有
- Is there a problem? - No.
他又知道什么
What does he know?
来吧罗西塔  辣妹得万众一心才行
Come on, Rosita. Us chicas gotta stick together.
你个贱人啊
You bitch!
罗斯
Hey, Ross?
我看了地产广告版
I checked the real estate section.
看这个
Look at this.
看上去像是爸妈的房子
Looks like Mom and Dad's house.
连院子里面前方树枝断掉的树都一样
Even has a tree with a broken limb out front.
阁楼的窗户
And the window in the attic...
天啊
Oh, my God!
阁楼的窗户怎么了
What happened to the window in the attic?
我不敢相信他们要把它卖掉
I can't believe they're selling it.
我不敢相信他们都没告诉我们
I can't believe they didn't even tell us.
我不敢相信我还是不知道
I can't believe I still don't know
阁楼的窗户到底怎么了
what happened to the window in the attic?
我会买张新椅子赔你  好吗
I'll buy you a new one, okay?
我们现在就去家具店  我立刻给你买张新的
We'll go to the store and get you a new chair right now.
她都还尸骨未寒呢
She's not even cold yet.
罗西塔也会希望你能继续生活的
Wouldn't Rosita have wanted you to move on?
她总以你为先
I mean, you know, she did always put your comfort first.
没错
That's true.
我不敢相信我们要向
I can't believe we have to say goodbye
承载我们成长记忆的房子说再见了
to the house we grew up in.
陌生人就要搬进我的房间里
Man, some stranger's gonna be in my room.
15年来  他们把你的房间搞得和神龛一样
For 15 years they kept it as a shrine to you.
是时候把紫罗兰绳子撤下来了
It's time the velvet ropes came down.
他们也为你保留了房间
They kept your room a while.
拜托  我搬出去才不过20分钟
Please! Dad turned my room
爸爸就把我的房间改造成健身房了
into a gym 20 minutes after I moved out.
我必须得说 美黑床
I gotta say, a tanning bed
外加一堆维多利亚秘密的内衣目录
and a stack of Victoria's Secret catalogs?
才不是健身房
Not a gym.
别这样  你知道他们爱你
Come on. You know they love you.
就跟他们爱你一样吗
As much as they love you?
我是头胎嘛
I was their first born.
在生我之前  他们都以为她不能生育
They thought she was barren until I was born.
又不是我的错
It's not my fault.
今年真讨厌
I hate this year.
今年怎么了
What's wrong with this year?
都二月了  我只给两位客人做过按摩
It's February and I've only given two massages...
而且他们给小费都给得很吝啬
...and they were both worst tippers in the world.
你是指我跟罗斯
That was me and Ross.
哦  没错
Oh, that's right.
如果你需要钱
If you want some extra cash...
我大学的朋友做电话行销赚了不少钱
...some college friends made good money doing telemarketing.
这次应该比我上次做有关电话的工作强
It'd be better than the last telephone job I had.
我大概不必常常说"打我屁股吧"
I probably won't have to say "Spank" As much.
什么
What?
对  你从来没打过那种电话
Oh, yeah, like you never called.
真的很简单  你只要照着稿子念
This is very easy. You read from the script...
试着多卖几盒墨盒
...and try to sell as much toner as you can.
我没问题的
Okay, I can do that.
对了  我喜欢我的办公室
By the way, I love my office.
-我们练习一下吧  -好啊
- Why don't we do a trial run? - Oh, okay.
好
All right.
我是帝国办公室文具公司的菲比
Hi, this is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
-能和总务部经历谈一下吗  -我就是
- Can I speak to your supply manager? - I'm the supply manager.
能谈谈你们的墨盒需求吗
I'd like to talk about your toner needs.
我们不需要墨盒
We don't need any toner.
抱歉打扰你  再见
Okay, sorry to bother you. Bye-bye.
你说对了  确实很容易
Yeah, you're right. This is easy.
那通电话什么地方做错了
Okay. What was wrong with that call?
就  好吧
Oh, well, all right.
恕我冒昧  你很粗鲁
No offense, but you were kind of rude.
他们总是说不需要墨盒  没关系
They always say they don't need toner. That's okay.
无论他们如何作答
Whatever they say,
你都可以在脚本中找到相应回答
you can find the answer to it, here in the script.
我想你准备好了
So I think you're ready to sell toner.
-还有问题吗  -没有
- Do you have any last questions? - No.
慢着  我有问题
Wait, yes, I do have one question:
墨盒是什么
What is toner?
乔伊
Joey?
Joe?
一整袋
Full bag?
啤酒还是冰的
Beer's still cold.
这里一定发生了很可怕的事
Something terrible must have happened here.
不不不
Oh, no, no, no!
史迪威  我没来过这里
Stevie, I was never here.
-爸  -我在这里
- Dad? - I'm here!
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
你们来看我工作
Seems like just yesterday
感觉还像昨天
you guys used to come out to watch me work.
我们不敢相信你们要卖掉房子
We can't believe you're selling the house.
是时候让新家庭在这里开始了
Time for a new family to start here.
我希望在支票兑现前他们不会发现
I hope their check clears before they find the crack...
地基有裂痕  天花板的石棉瓦破了
...in the foundation and the asbestos in the ceiling.
我们快把东西拿一拿  离开这里吧
Let's grab our stuff and get the hell out of here.
抱歉不能继续保留你们孩提时代的玩具了
Sorry we can't store your things.
没事
Oh, it's okay.
我迫不及待想要再看看那些东西
I can't wait to see everything again.
我不知道那些盒子里都存了些什么
I don't know what's those boxes down here.
但我知道阁楼上有六七箱简易烘焙烤箱
But I do know there are six or seven Easy-Bake Ovens in the attic.
我以前最喜欢玩开餐厅的游戏了
I used to love to play restaurant.
但你最爱的还是"吃面粉糊"游戏
Not as much as you loved to play "Uncooked batter eater."
你不能要求
You can't expect a child
小孩子等着电灯泡把巧克力蛋糕烤熟
to wait for a light bulb to cook brownies.
我想你的箱子应该都在这里
So I think your boxes are over here.
太棒了
Oh, great.
嘿
Hey...
这是谁的烟
...whose cigarettes are these?
我不知道
I don't know.
一定是你妈的
They must be your mother's.
求求你别去质问她  我来把烟丢掉
But please, please don't ask her. I'll throw these away.
酷  爸  是我的成绩单
Cool! Dad, my report cards!
快来看
Hey, check this out.
数学"优等"  自然"优等"
Math, "A." Science, "A."
历史"优等"  体育
History, "A." Gym...
我的磨石机
My rock polisher!
-哎呦  -怎么了
- Uh-oh. - What?
你知道每年春天车库都会淹水吗
You know how the garage floods every spring?
你怎么会想把房子卖掉呢
How are you ever gonna sell this place?
我想我不小心把莫妮卡的箱子
I think I accidentally used Monica's boxes...
用来挡水  好让保时捷不被淹
...to keep the water away from the Porsche.
不  爸爸  爸
Oh, no, Dad. Dad?
这也太
What the...
所有的东西都毁了
Oh, God. Everything's ruined!
爸  她一定会崩溃的
Dad, she's gonna be crushed.
你没有偷偷学抽烟吧
You don't secretly smoke, do you?
没有
No.
那这就是你妈妈的了
So it's just your mother then.
我是帝国办公室文具公司的菲比
Hi. This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
请问总务部经理在吗
Can I speak to your supply manager, please?
厄尔  谢谢
Earl. Thanks.
厄尔  我是帝国办公室文具公司的菲比
Hi, Earl. This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
我想和你谈谈你们的墨盒需求
I'd like to talk to you about your toner needs.
我不需要墨盒
I don't need any toner.
哦我知道了
I hear what you're saying,
但是以我们的价格来说  人人都需要墨盒
but at our prices, everyone needs toner.
我不要
Not me.
我能问下原因吗
May I ask why?
你想知道原因
You want to know why?
当然
I surely do.
好
Okay.
我不需要墨盒
I don't need any toner...
因为我即将自杀
...because I'm gonna kill myself.
就因为你们没墨盒了吗
Is that because you're out of toner?
反正就是不要墨盒  谢谢  再见
Okay, so no toner today. Thanks anyway. Bye-bye.
等一下 我不能让你挂电话  请跟我说话
Wait, wait! I can't let you hang up. Just please talk to me.
就
Well...
今天我只需要做一件事
I only had one thing to do today.
我猜我能把它延期一下吧
I guess I could push it back.
好吧  你为什么要自杀
Yeah. Now, why do you want to kill yourself?
十年来  我一直在做
I've been working for 10 years now at this...
这份没有意义没有前途的工作
...meaningless, dead-end job...
办公室里的人根本不知道我的存在
...and nobody here even knows that I exist.
钱德勒
Chandler?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
听着
Look...
我相信他们都知道你的存在
...l'm sure that people know you exist.
我就在个小格子里工作
Oh, yeah? I work in a cubicle...
四周都是人
...surrounded by people.
我已经跟你谈了五分钟
I've been talking to you
我要自杀的问题
for five minutes now about killing myself...
都没有人抬头来看我一眼  等一下
...and no one's even looked up from their desk. Hang on.
大伙们
Hey, everybody...
我要自杀了
...l'm gonna kill myself.
没人理我
I got nothing.
好样的  椅子
Good chair.
如果有人问起
Now, if anybody asks...
你就叫罗西塔
...your name is Rosita.
真可怜  英年早逝
Poor thing. Cut down in her prime.
乔伊  新椅子一小时内就到
Joey, the new chair will be here in an hour.
也许你该把罗西塔移出去
Maybe we should move Rosita out of here.
开始疗伤过程
Start the healing process.
你说得对
Yeah, I guess you're right.
她痊愈了
She's healed!
-那太奇怪  -一点都不奇怪
- That's weird. - No, it's not weird.
这是奇迹
It's a miracle!
这不是奇迹  一定有合理的解释
It's not a miracle. I'm sure there's an explanation.
只要你的心地纯良  奇迹一定会发生
There is. If your heart is pure, wondrous things can happen.
她会了解的  我不是故意的
She'll understand. I didn't do it on purpose.
爸  那不是重点
Dad, that won't matter to her.
你看  我的箱子完全没事
Look, all my stuff is safe and dry.
她的东西都
And all her stuff is...
长出新的东西了
...growing new stuff.
就是这样的事
This is the kind of thing...
让她认为你们爱我更胜于爱她
...that makes her think you love me more than her.
天啊  她真的那么认为
My God. Does she think that?
-你能怪她吗  -我不知道
- Can you blame her? - I don't know.
或许我们在潜意识上是偏爱你的
We may have favored you unconsciously.
你是个医学奇迹
You were a medical marvel.
医生都说你母亲无法
The doctors said your mom couldn't...
我不想听
I don't want to hear it.
-真的吗  -现在不想听
- Really? - Well, not right now.
莫妮卡来这里找回忆
Monica came here for some memories.
该死  我们得给她一些回亿
Damn it, we'll give her some.
好吧  拿
Okay, grab...
把空箱子拿过来  我们拿一些我的东西
Grab some empty boxes. We'll take stuff from mine...
只要能和她扯上关系的  就放在这些箱子里
...and whatever we can pass off as hers, we'll put in there.
-类似这个  她有可能会做这个  -对
- Like, this. She could have made this - Sure.
-这个也可能是她的  -对
- This could have been hers. - Sure.
我好高兴我能把这张椅子留下来给自己用
I am so psyched I kept this chair for myself.
对  我也是
Yeah. Me too.
你知道这张椅子的头枕上还附了喇叭吗
You know, this thing has speakers in the headrest?
-不知道  真的吗  -对
- No, really? - Yeah.
你可以把它跟电视机接在一起还可以听收音机
You can hook it to the TV and you get radio.
我的椅子能自愈
My chair heals itself.
好吧  我们别提
All right. Let's just forget
办公室的同事了
about the people at the office, okay?
一定有人值得你留恋
There's gotta be someone won'th sticking around for.
你的家人跟朋友呢  女朋友呢
What about family or friends? Maybe a girlfriend?
是啊
Yeah, right.
抱歉  那就是男朋友
Oh, sorry. Boyfriend?
好了  我应该
Okay, I should...
去做我想做的事了
...be getting back to my thing now.
再见
See you.
我还没有说完  你休想挂我电话
I'm not finished! Don't you dare hang up on me!
新来的姑娘有一套啊
The new girl's good.
哪些箱子是我的
Which boxes are mine?
-你的箱子在这里  -好吧
- These are yours right here. - Okay.
着色簿
A coloring book.
你喜欢那玩意
You loved that thing.
你去哪里都会
You never went anywhere without...
都会带着那本着色簿
...without that coloring book.
真的吗
Really?
看起来我老是没办法把颜色涂在线里
Looks like I had trouble staying in the lines.
看这个
Wow, look at this.
我不敢相信以前我穿得下这件T恤
I can't believe I even fit into this shirt.
噢  这是你的
Oh, this is yours.
我不知道它怎么会跑到那里去
I don't know how that got in there.
这些不是我的东西
Hey, this isn't my stuff.
罗斯  这些是你的箱子
Ross, these are your boxes.
我的箱子在哪里
Where are my boxes?
车库淹水甜心  你的箱子都进了水  对不起
The garage flooded, sweetie, and ruined your boxes. I'm sorry.
只有我的淹了
Just mine?
恐怕是这样
I'm afraid so.
为什么罗斯的东西都没坏
Why wasn't Ross' stuff ruined?
我用你的箱子挡水  保护我的保时捷
I used your boxes to divert water away from the Porsche.
罗斯的东西都没事  但我的回忆都没有了
Ross' stuff is fine, but I have no memories...
只因为你不希望自己车的底盘不碰到水
...so you could keep the bottom of your car from water?
水里有树叶  泥巴跟杂物
There was also leaves and gook and stuff.
我不敢相信
I can't believe this!
去他的  我要抽根烟
Screw it. I'm having one.
-嘿  钱德勒  -嘿
- Hey, Chandler. - Hey.
你要不要试试看一张可以平躺
How'd you like to sit in a chair that reclines...
有滚轮按摩功能
...has a rolling massage...
头枕上还有喇叭的椅子
...and speakers in the headrest?
我试过很多次
I've tried that so many times...
但他们已经不再让我走进他们店里
...they won't even let me in the store anymore.
如果我说你可以到我家试坐一下呢
What if I said you could do it in my apartment?
你是在告诉我
Are you telling me...
你买了那张让其他椅子都变成废物的椅子
...you bought the chair that makes all others obsolete?
那张《座椅杂志》称其为年度座椅的椅子
The chair that Sit Magazine called "Chair of the Year"?
我刚刚买了
I just purchased...
懒人E倾斜3000型
...the La-Z-Boy E-Cliner 3000.
那真的是太棒了  你为什么买下它
Well, that's awesome! That's great! What made you do it?
说来话长  但我弄坏了乔伊的椅子
It's a long story, but, I broke Joey's chair...
是你弄坏了乔伊的椅子
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You broke Joey's chair?
我以为是我干的  所以我用我的椅子调了包
I thought I did, that's why I replaced it with mine.
它是这么被修好的
That's how it got fixed!
你以为是妖精把它修好的
You thought that elves came in and fixed it?
不是
No.
是天使干的
Angels.
我要把我的椅子拿回来
I'm getting my chair back.
看起来这椅子没自愈成功啊
Well, looks like it wasn't healed after all!
这椅子是我的了
I guess this chair's mine now.
乔伊  你弄坏了我的椅子
Joey, you broke my chair!
你的
Your chair?
他以为他把它弄坏了  所以他掉了包
He thought he broke it, so he switched chairs.
奇迹根本不存在
So there was no miracle?
没错  乔伊  奇迹不存在
No, Joe. No miracle.
这真的是太糟糕了
Oh, no! This is devastating!
我的信念被击垮了
My faith is shaken.
我很高兴这张新椅子能陪我走过这一切
I'm glad I have a new chair to get me through this.
我在哪能找到厄尔  总务部经理
Where can I find Earl? He's the supply manager here.
我不认识厄尔
I don't know any Earl.
我在这
I'm right here!
厄尔
Earl?
我是菲比
I'm Phoebe.
菲比
Phoebe?
卖墨盒的小姐
The lady who sells toner?
听着  你不能自杀
Look, you can't kill yourself.
我很感激你赶过来
Look, I really appreciate you coming down...
我不能让你那么做
No, I can't let you do it.
-为什么  -因为命运让我今天给你打了电话
- Why? - Because, fate made me call you today.
我以为你是为了墨盒
I thought it was toner.
好好想一想  好吗  这根本不是我的正职
Think about it, okay? This isn't even my regular job.
我第一天上班第一个电话  就是打给你
My first day, you're my first call.
其他人可能会挂掉电话  但我不会那么做
Somebody else may have hung up, but I wouldn't do that...
因为我了解这种事
...because I know about this stuff.
-我妈是自杀的  -真的吗
- My mom killed herself. - Really?
怎么自杀的
How?
我不会给你自杀温馨小贴士的
I'm not gonna give you tips.
你看不出来
Don't you see that this...
这些都是注定的  所以我才会来阻止你自杀
...all came together so I could stop you from doing this?
-这不是巧合吗  -这是命中注定
- Couldrt it just be a coincidence? - No, it's fate.
它看起来不像是命中注定
It doesn't really seem like enough to be fate.
好吧
Oh, well.
有件事很奇怪
Okay, here's a weird thing.
我妈妈也是总务部经理
My mother was also a supply manager.
事实上我是办公室经理
I'm actually the office manager.
我的天啊  她也是
Oh, my God! So was she!
还有这个
And get this, okay.
你叫厄尔  对吧  她叫做普厄儿
Your name is Earl, right? Her name was Pearl.
普厄尔
Puh-Earl.
还有别的证据吗
Was there anything else?
当然
Sure.
你是哪里人
Where're you from?
-费城  -我的天啊  她也是
- Philadelphia. - Oh, my God, so was she!
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I've got goose bumps.
-是吗  -我穿太多  这里太热
- Really? - I'm wearing layers, and it's warm.
或许这些混蛋不在乎你
These jerks might not care about you...
但宇宙在乎你  那才是最重要的
...but the universe does, and that says a lot.
你们听到了吗
Did you hear that?
我不需要你们在乎我
I don't need you guys to care about me...
因为宇宙在乎我
...because the universe cares!
整个宇宙在乎我
The whole universe!
我真的希望他们能在乎我一下
I really wish they'd care a little bit.
这真的是太可怕了
Oh, this is terrible.
所有的东西都毁了
Everything is destroyed.
看这个
Look at this.
对我意义重大我才收起来
It meant enough for me to save,
但现在我不知道这是什么了
and now I can't tell what it is.
还是很柔软
It's still soft.
你觉得它是什么呢
What do you think this is?
老鼠吧
I think it was a mouse.
-你还好吗 甜心  -你觉得呢
- How are you, honey? - How do you think I am?
你毁了我的儿时记忆
You've wrecked my childhood memories...
你们只爱罗斯
...you love Ross more than me.
我刚刚还拿死老鼠摩挲了我的脸
And I just rubbed a dead mouse on my face.
甜心  我们爱你和爱罗斯一样多
Sweetheart, we love you just as much as Ross.
箱子的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about everything that happened...
也许我永远没办法补偿你
...and I probably can't make it up to you...
但这是个开始
...but here's a start.
-这是什么  -我保时捷的钥匙
- What's this? - It's the key to my Porsche.
你保时捷的钥匙
Well, the key to your Porsche.
什么
What?
What?!
我一直想把它处理掉  那天我开着它在外面
I've been thinking getting rid of it. I was driving it the other day.
我在后视镜里看到自己的倒影
I saw my reflection on the window.
你妈说的对  我看起来像个混球
Your mother's right, I do look like an ass.
你要把它送给我  你一定是在开玩笑
You're giving it to me? You're kidding.
等一下
Well, wait a minute.
几只愚蠢的箱子湿了  她就能有保时捷
A couple of stupid boxes get wet, and she gets a Porsche?
-我们去兜风吧  -太帅了
- Let's take it for a spine? - All right!
我呢  我是医学奇迹
What about me? I'm a medical marvel!
嘿  你们都在
Hey, guys.
你们看到钱德勒的椅子了吗
Have you seen Chandler's chair?
乔伊把它弄折了  扔了
Joey broke it. He got rid of it.
开玩笑吗  我得到了保时捷躺椅也没了
Are you kidding? I get a Porsche and the Barcalounger's gone?
这是有史以来最棒的一天
This is the best day ever!